对于Sunshine这个程序来说  这些信息只是理论上的
For the purposes of the Sunshine app, this information is purely theoretical.
事实上  当你需要加入一些特殊的操作  如传感监听器
In fact, you'll really only need to consider this later,
或者定位监听器的时候  你才真正需要考虑这个问题
when you're adding things like Sensor or LocationListeners. Until then,
到目前为止  默认的组件能帮你完成大多数操作
the default components will handle much of this behavior for
总之  你现在了解了生命周期
you. In any case, now that you understand the lifecycle and
和当系统需要资源时  它会如何让你的应用退出
the way the system handles exiting your app, when it needs its resources.
你也应该明白为什么退出或者停止键在Android应用中 其实
You should hopefully understand why Exit or Quit buttons in Android apps serve
并没有实际的意义  最多  也就是你可以通过在Activity中调用Finish函数
no practical purpose. At most, you can call finish on an activity and
让你的应用马上结束  当你点击返回键时
it will get torn down instantly. That's actually exactly what happens when
实际上表现的就是上述的行为
you use a simple hits back from within their activity.
如果你还是无法确信的话  可以打开在指导手册里的视频
If you're still not convinced, check out the video in the instructor notes.
我在那个视频里对原因做了更加生动的讲述
Where I explain my reasoning with a little more, color.